THE CHARACTERS, ORGANIZATIONS AND EVENTS OF THIS DRAMA ARE FICTIONAL
本剧的人物、组织和 事件均为虚构
Bloody hell!
该死的！
Kill her!
杀了她！
What are you doing?
你在干什么？
Go ahead, kill him!
来吧，杀了他！
Damned!
该死！
Find out what Jung Gicheul is up to
看看郑基哲在做什么
and where he goes with whom.
以及他和谁一起去哪里。
Keep us informed about it.
让我们随时了解情况。
Dirt pigs!
土猪！
Damn son of a bitch!
该死的王八蛋！
You motherfuckers!
你们这些混蛋！
Fuck!
他妈的！
Hyeok is in the emergency room.
赫在急诊室。
I can't go fishing tomorrow.
明天我不能去钓鱼了。
You two go alone.
你们两个单独去吧。
Hi, Boss.
嗨，老板。
I have a flat tire and am stuck.
我的轮胎漏气了 ，被困住了。
Excuse me.
打扰一下。
Can you move on already?
你可以继续了吗？
What are you fucking doing?
你他妈在做什么？
Young Gicheul.
年轻的吉切尔。
You Hurensohn!
你这个胡伦森！
Fuck!
他妈的！
Do I look like a sneaky traitor, you son of a bitch?
我看起来像个 狡猾的叛徒吗，你这个王八蛋？
Seung Ho.
胜浩
Get in quickly.
快点进去吧。
You shit!
你妈的！
Damned!
该死！
Seung Ho.
胜浩
Kwon Seungho!
权胜浩！
Come on. Wake up.
快点。醒来。
Seungho, stay with me.
胜浩，留在我身边吧。
Go ahead!
前进！
THE WORST OF EVIL
最邪恶的事
OPERATION
手术
-We need a lot of bandages. -Yes, doctor.
-我们需要很多绷带。 -是的，医生。
-It's bleeding a lot. -Yes.
-流了很多血。 -是的。
-Do not touch the wound. -OK.
- 不要触摸伤口。 -好的。
-Mortgage. - Ok.
-抵押。 - 好的。
OPERATION
手术
Something happened on the way to the port.
在去港口的路上发生了一些事情。
I am fully responsible.
我负全部责任。
Was that China, boss?
老板，那是中国吗？
The Japanese should also be called.
日本人也应该这样称呼。
Wait outside.
等在外面。
Yes, boss.
是的，老板。
Chief Seo.
徐局长.
You know who knew besides the three of us
你知道除了我们三个之外还有谁知道
that I went fishing, right?
我去钓鱼了，对吗？
Yes, Sir.
是的先生。
Heesung, Jungbae, Kyungjin, Byungwoo.
熙成、正裴、庆珍、秉宇。
Find out who is in cahoots with Jaegeon.
找出谁 与 Jaegeon 勾结。
You're the only one I can trust.
你是我唯一 可以信任的人。
Yes, boss.
是的，老板。
Hallo.
你好。
Were you recently called by a Mercedes with a flat tire?
您最近是否 接到过一辆爆胎的奔驰车的电话？
Ah, that one.
啊，那个。
I'm there,
我在那里，
and the guy was totally unfriendly and just pushed.
那家伙完全 不友好，只是推搡。
There he is.
他在那。
Must have driven very aggressively.
一定是驾驶得非常激进。
An unusual crack.
不寻常的裂缝。
Is Seungho okay?
胜浩还好吗？
Is Gicheul still in the hospital?
吉切尔还在医院吗？
And.
和。
These pigs will pay for it.
这些猪会为此付出代价。
Thanks.
谢谢。
I was in the office the whole time that day.
那天我一直在办公室。
I watched a video with him,
我和他一起看了一个视频
and that night we had a drink in his bar.
那天晚上 我们在他的酒吧喝了一杯。
Before that we played pool.
在那之前我们打台球。
Exactly. We also went to a pool hall.
确切地。我们还去 了台球厅。
Dont move. Hold still.
别动。静止不动。
I'll get help.
我会寻求帮助。
Captain Seok talks to the doctors.
石船长与医生交谈。
-Worry... -You are irresponsible.
-担心... -你不负责任。
They knew about the turf war with Song Donghyuk's gang.
他们知道 与宋东赫帮的地盘争夺战。
Did he really have to be alone there?
他真的必须一个人在那里吗？
Couldn't you take any precautions?
你就不能采取一些预防措施吗？
Have local support available?
有本地支持吗？
We cannot predict every scenario.
我们无法 预测每一种情况。
It is normal for unexpected situations to arise.
出现意外情况是正常的。
And you want to go through with it after everything that's happened.
在发生这一切之后你想要经历这一切。
Did it help Junmo in any way...
对俊莫有什么帮助吗……
... that I met Jung Gicheul?
……我遇见了郑基哲？
If so, I want to help more actively.
如果是这样，我想更积极地提供帮助。
If I can get my husband out of there unharmed,
如果我 能让我丈夫毫发无伤地离开那里
I meet Jung Gicheul and play along.
我遇见了郑基哲并一起玩。
Anything to end this crazy operation quickly!
不惜一切代价 尽快结束这场疯狂的行动！
That was the second time you saved my life.
那是你第二次 救了我的命。
I trust you now.
我现在信任你了。
Boss.
老板。
If so,
如果是这样，
can I have a cigarette?
我可以抽烟吗？
No product for us?
没有适合我们的产品？
We didn't even meet the Korean captain.
我们甚至没有见到 韩国队长。
No news from them?
他们没有消息吗？
No. His phone is turned off.
不，他的手机已关机。
The payment was in advance, right?
是提前付款的吧？
Yes, Boss.
是的，老板。
Tried to reach her.
试图联系她。
Because of the fishing trip...
因为去钓鱼...
Are you really going fishing?
你真的要去钓鱼吗？
Middle of the night?
半夜？
At least the sailing part, yes.
至少航行部分，是的。
For what?
为了什么？
After all that , I have a right to know.
毕竟 ，我有权利知道。
Is it some kind of smuggling at sea?
这是某种海上走私吗？
Everything in its time.
一切都在它的时间里。
Found out what?
发现什么了吗？
Not yet, sir.
还没有，先生。
I think I know who it is.
我想我知道他是谁。
Who is it, sir?
先生是谁？
Send everyone back to Seoul.
送大家回首尔。
They are supposed to gather at the office at 9:00 p.m.
他们预计晚上 9:00 在办公室集合
Every single one.
每一个。
Yes, boss.
是的，老板。
And first tell them
并首先告诉他们
we would know who sold our gang to Jaegeon.
我们就会知道是谁 把我们的团伙卖给了Jaegeon。
And that I will punish the rat in front of everyone.
我 会当着所有人的面惩罚这只老鼠。
Yes, boss.
是的，老板。
Bon Voyage. See you there.
一路顺风。到时候那里见。
JEIL HOSPITAL
第一医院
Moment. I have a question.
片刻。我有个问题。
How are the guys who got shot doing?
那些 被枪杀的人现在怎么样了？
They're all alive, don't worry.
他们都还活着， 不用担心。
Instead, worry about yourself.
相反，担心你自己。
Give me the key.
把钥匙给我。
Boss.
老板。
INTERNATIONAL, JAPAN
国际、日本
-Hello. -You son of a bitch.
-你好。 -你个​​王八蛋。
You dare to ignore our call?
你敢 无视我们的召唤吗？
Do you think we can't find you with our money?
你以为 我们有钱就找不到你吗？
Do you think that?
你这么认为吗？
It's me.
这就是我。
What happened?
发生了什么？
On the way to the sea
去海边的路上
Song Donghyuk's men attacked us.
宋东赫的人袭击了我们。
One of us almost died.
我们中的一个人差点就死了。
An ambush?
伏击？
That means they knew
这意味着他们知道
which route you would take.
你会走哪条路线。
I also just noticed that I was being watched.
我也刚刚注意到 我正在被监视。
There must be a rat
一定有一只老鼠
under your command.
在你的指挥下。
Do you have anything to say about that?
对此你有什么要说的吗？
No.
不。
Either way, you are responsible for what happened.
不管怎样，你都要 对所发生的事情负责。
What do we do?
我们做什么？
Start the car!
启动汽车！
So really.
真的。
Hey.
嘿。
Is not it ...
是不是 ...
... really tight in here for you?
...这里对你来说真的很紧吗？
You can make yourself comfortable.
你可以让自己舒服一点。
Do you want to emulate Chow Yun-fat or what?
你想效仿周润发 还是什么？
Wherever you go, there is war.
走到哪里，哪里就有战争。
But somehow you never die doing it.
但不知怎的，你永远不会死。
Just like in A Better Tomorrow.
就像《美好明天》里的那样。
Man, Chow Yung-fat is so cool.
周永发真是太帅了
It would have been perfect with sticks.
如果有棍子就完美了。
You probably fought like that too.
想必你也曾这样战斗过。
Total irre.
完全不。
RASTHOF JINJONG
拉斯特霍夫·金钟
I'm going to the bathroom.
我要去卫生间。
Ok.
好的。
It seems you have to too.
看来你也必须这么做。
I'll do it very quickly.
我会很快做的。
Ow, my stomach.
哎呀，我的胃。
That hurts!
好痛啊！
Junmo.
Junmo.
Are you OK?
你还好吗？
I almost died.
我差点死了。
I'm sorry.
对不起。
It's ok.
没关系。
Gicheul actually seems to be smuggling when he goes fishing.
吉彻尔去钓鱼时，实际上似乎是在走私。
And tonight
还有今晚
he wants to kill the gang's traitor.
他想杀死该团伙的叛徒。
We have to prevent that.
我们必须防止这种情况发生。
OK. Take care.
好的。小心。
I'll do it.
我会做的。
INCOMING CALL
来电
Hallo?
哈啰？
Incheon port in two days?
仁川港两天？
Are you coming here?
你要来了吗？
In order.
为了。
I'll make the salutation easier for you.
我会让你更容易地称呼你。
Seungho is the oldest here,
Seungho是这里最年长的，
From now on you will call him "Sir".
从现在起你就称呼他为“先生”。
Ok?
好的？
Yes, boss.
是的，老板。
Louder, you bastards!
大声一点，你们这些混蛋！
Yes, boss!
是的，老板！
Do you know who sold us...
你知道是谁卖了我们吗？
... to the Jaegeon group?
……去Jaegeon集团？
Good to meet you.
很高兴见到你。
If you decline, someone else will accept our offer.
如果您拒绝，其他人 就会接受我们的报价。
Think about it carefully.
仔细想一想。
Look around
环视四周
and look who isn't here,
看看谁不在这里，
because they don't want to die.
因为他们不想死。
Kyungjin, Byungwoo und Chief Seo.
Kyungjin、Byungwoo 和 Chief Seo。
I don't see the three.
没看到三人啊
Sorry. I couldn't get a taxi.
对不起。我打不到出租车。
Who is the traitor?
谁是叛徒？
I think not Heesung or Jungbae.
我认为 不是熙星或正裴。
They're all alive, don't worry.
他们都还活着， 不用担心。
Oh Kyungjin.
噢，京津。
We should find him and get him away quickly.
我们应该 尽快找到他并把他带走。
He was the only one who knew the situation in the Jaegeon group.
他是唯一知道 宰建集团情况的人。
Oh Kyungjin.
噢，京津。
Hallo?
哈啰？
Kyungjin?
京津？
Yes, Boss.
是的，老板。
Oh Kyungjin.
噢，京津。
Oh Kyungjin!
京津啊！
Damned.
该死的。
Fuck.
他妈的。
Fuck ...
他妈的 ...
Kyungjin, why did you do it?
京津，你为什么这么做？
Why are you asking me this?
你为什么问我这个？
It's shameful for me.
这对我来说是可耻的。
Yeah, that's not important, is it?
是的，这并不重要，不是吗？
What matters is you caused this mess.
重要的是 你造成了这个混乱。
I want you to see
我希望你能看到
what happens when you cheat on your family.
当你欺骗你的家人时会发生什么。
Chief Seo.
徐局长.
Fuck.
他妈的。
Boss.
老板。
Fuck!
他妈的！
What are you planning to do now?
你现在打算做什么？
That bastard almost cost you your life.
那个混蛋 差点要了你的命。
He has to pay for that.
他必须为此付出代价。
Try to endure it.
尝试去忍受它。
Because it will hurt.
因为会痛。
You fucking son of a bitch.
你他妈的王八蛋。
Let's see it.
让我们来看看它。
Damn son of a bitch. Mieses Dreckschwein.
该死的王八蛋。 米塞斯·德雷克施韦因。
Damn sneaky rat.
该死的狡猾的老鼠。
Stupid trash bag.
愚蠢的垃圾袋。
Damn son of a bitch.
该死的王八蛋。
You piece of shit.
你这个废物。
I almost died because of you, you fucker.
我差点因为你而死， 你这个混蛋。
OK? Fucking traitor.
好的？他妈的叛徒。
Boss.
老板。
That should be enough for him almost killing me.
这对他来说已经足够了， 差点杀了我。
-Hey, Yongdae. -Ja, Sir.
-嘿，龙大。 -贾，先生。
Stay out of my sight.
远离我的视线。
If I see you again, I'll kill you.
如果我再见到你， 我会杀了你。
Heesung, Jungbae, Chief Seo, follow me.
熙星、正裴、徐局长，跟我来。
You too, Seungho.
你也是，胜浩。
Consider yourself lucky, you bastard.
想想自己很幸运吧，你这个混蛋。
Clean up here.
清理这里。
Yes, Sir!
是的先生！
Throw him far away.
把他扔到很远的地方。
Yes, Sir.
是的先生。
The Chinese are coming in two days.
两天后中国人就来了。
Why all of a sudden?
为什么突然？
Why don't we talk about this more privately, sir?
先生，我们为什么不 私下谈谈这个问题呢？
No, we need more than just the three of us now.
不，我们 现在需要的不仅仅是我们三个人。
You already know what's going on, right?
你已经知道发生了什么事，对吧？
I'll take care of her.
我会照顾她的。
Prepare something that will brighten her mood.
准备一些 能让她心情愉悦的东西。
Yes, Boss.
是的，老板。
And Heesung,
还有熙成，
find out if Kyungjin is up to something.
看看京津是不是在搞什么鬼。
Ok.
好的。
Seo, take care of Seungho.
徐，照顾好胜浩。
Yes, Boss.
是的，老板。
You can go.
你可以走了。
HIDEOUT IN DONGHOBANG CHINA
中国东和帮的藏身处
SEOUL, DISTRICT ATTORNEY OF SOUTH KOREA
韩国首尔地方检察官
DRUG MANUFACTURERS CONVICTED DRUG OFFENDERS
毒品制造商 被定罪为毒品犯罪者
Among those convicted of meth
在因吸食冰毒而被定罪的人中
we examined all the meth cooks.
我们检查了所有的冰毒厨师。
YOON WONGIL
尹旺日
Yoon Wongil.
尹元一.
Why did she still go to China?
她为什么还要去中国？
To travel.
去旅行。
She's not back?
她还没回来？
No.
不。
Traveling in China for half a year?
来中国旅游半年？
Get the interpreter.
找个翻译。
Ich rufe Mr. Murayama an.
我很生气村山先生。
Yes, Sir.
是的先生。
-Captain Seok? -Hallo, Sir.
-石船长？ -你好，先生。
Do you know Professor Yoon?
你认识尹教授吗？
Die grauhaarige Dame.
Die grauhaarige 女士。
I have something big here.
我这里有件大事。
This trade could not only Korea and Japan,
这种贸易 不仅可以韩国和日本，
but affect Korea, China and Japan.
但影响韩国、中国和日本。
The Chinese are now among our suspects.
中国人现在已成为 我们的嫌疑人之一。
If Detective Park attends the meeting with the Chinese tomorrow,
如果朴侦探 明天参加与中国人的会面的话
we can better evaluate this theory .
我们可以更好地评价这个理论。
Do we ask him for help?
我们向他寻求帮助吗？
NATIONAL DRUG COMMISSIONER BEIJING, CHINA
国家药品监督管理局 中国北京
WANTED YOON WONGIL, KOREAN, 73
通缉 YOON WONGIL, 韩国人, 73 岁
Hallo?
哈啰？
Hi, Gicheul. It's me, Euijeong.
嗨，吉切尔。是我，义正。
Hi, Euijeong.
嗨，义正。
I should have called you.
我应该给你打电话的。
How are you doing? Are you OK?
你好吗？你还好吗？
Yes, thank you.
是的，谢谢。
Thank you for coming to the funeral.
感谢您前来 参加葬礼。
You don't have to thank me, that was my duty.
你不用谢我， 那是我的职责。
Speaking of which,
说到这，
are you free tomorrow?
你明天有空吗？
Morning?
早晨？
Yes, tomorrow is the only day I have free.
是的，明天是我唯一 有空的一天。
Can we meet?
我们能碰面吗？
Yes that works. Let's meet tomorrow.
是的，这有效。 我们明天见。
Say Seungho please
请说胜浩
that I would also like to thank him for his visit.
我还要 感谢他的来访。
I will do.
我会做。
I have an important appointment tomorrow.
明天我有一个重要的约会。
You take care of the Chinese.
你照顾中国人。
What happened?
发生了什么？
Yes, boss.
是的，老板。
Have you checked hospitals?
你检查过医院吗？
Boss.
老板。
Can I answer that with Chief Seo?
我可以 和 Seo 局长一起回答这个问题吗？
Finish eating first.
先吃完再说。
Yes, Boss.
是的，老板。
Heesung.
熙成.
What's your baby's name?
你的宝宝叫什么名字？
Jaeyoung.
杰瑛.
Hong Jaeyoung.
洪在瑛.
That's a great name.
这是一个很棒的名字。
I'm coming to visit.
我来参观一下。
Secure. The baby is so sweet.
安全的。宝宝真甜啊。
Doesn't look like me at all.
看起来一点也不像我。
It looks like Hyeok.
看起来像赫赫。
What did you want to say in confidence?
你想私下说什么？
Chief Seo.
徐局长.
You investigated where Oh Kyungjin was that day, right?
你调查了 吴庆镇那天在哪里吧？
Naturally.
自然。
I'm just wondering
我是在想
how to locate our car
如何找到我们的车
and could inform them.
并可以通知他们。
He didn't chase our car.
他没有追我们的车。
Jungbae followed us that day.
那天，正裴跟着我们。
Do you suspect Jungbae?
你怀疑郑培吗？
You too, Chief Seo?
徐局长你也是吗？
Yes, I have that suspicion too.
是的，我也有这样的怀疑。
Boss.
老板。
Let's do one final check.
让我们做最后一项检查。
Our guests from China
我们来自中国的客人
seem important to our business.
似乎对我们的业务很重要。
How about sending Seungho while I check on Jungbae?
我去看看中裴的时候，让胜浩过来怎么样 ？
You should be careful
你应该小心
until we are sure about Jungbae and Heesung.
直到我们 确定了 Jungbae 和 Heesung 的情况。
Jungbae is like my little brother.
Jungbae就像我的弟弟。
Do it professionally.
专业地做。
Yes, Boss.
是的，老板。
Chief Seo.
徐局长.
You can leave. Do it right.
你可以走了。做对了。
Yes, Boss.
是的，老板。
Hallo, Boss.
你好，老板。
You have the information on all of my people, right?
你有我所有人的信息，对吗？
Yes, I have.
是的，我有。
I need to do some research.
我需要做一些 研究。
If everything goes right,
如果一切顺利的话
The old goes out and the new comes in.
旧的出去 ，新的进来。
You called, sir?
先生，你打电话来了吗？
Do you have any gifts for the Chinese?
你有什么礼物送给中国人吗？
Yes, I have something expensive ready.
是的，我准备了一些昂贵的东西。
Good job.
好工作。
Thanks, boss.
谢谢老板。
Also ...
还 ...
... I would like to drink something,
……我想喝点东西，
but I don't want to drink alone.
但我不想一个人喝酒。
And.
和。
Great. I was just about to grab a drink myself.
伟大的。我正想 自己去喝一杯。
Should I prepare the drinks outside?
我应该在外面准备饮料吗？
Sounds good.
听起来不错。
Ok, Sir.
好的，先生。
PATROL PROTOCOL
巡逻协议
Sir.
先生。
Sir?
先生？
A simple survey.
一个简单的调查。
You can answer my questions with a nod.
你可以 点头回答我的问题。
Our investigation is stuck here.
我们的调查就到此为止了。
How did you know which route Jung Gicheul would take?
你怎么知道 郑基哲会走哪条路？
Did someone track his car and tell them?
有人跟踪他的车 并告诉他们吗？
Then how did you know?
那你怎么知道的？
Did your gang follow his car,
你们的帮派有没有跟踪他的车？
all the way from Seoul?
从首尔一路过来？
With the car you were in?
和你坐的车一起吗？
Aber Sir, ...
阿伯先生，...
... You were shot,
...你被枪杀了，
but that you don't recognize my face?
但你 不认识我的脸？
I'm Seo Jongryeol.
我是徐钟烈。
Nice to talk to you alone,
很高兴与你单独交谈
without the other boys.
没有其他男孩。
It's been a while.
有一阵子了。
Please.
请。
And.
和。
I'm sending Kwon Seungho
我送权胜浩
tomorrow morning to Icheon port.
明天一早去利川港。
Get some rest.
休息一下。
Yes, Boss.
是的，老板。
That's life.
这就是生活。
It always gets you in the end.
它总是能最终帮助你。
Take it like that.
就这样吧。
And this,
和这个，
like sinking into peaceful sleep.
就像陷入平静的睡眠中一样。
Since you bring it up...
既然你提出来了...
Also ...
还 ...
Just in case...
万一...
Just to be sure,
只是要确定，
You didn't suspect me or Heesung, did you?
你没有 怀疑我和熙成吧？
What are you talking about?
你在说什么？
Correct.
正确的。
Sorry. Forget it, boss.
对不起。忘了吧，老板。
Hallo?
哈啰？
Boss, this is Jongryeol.
老板，这是钟烈。
As per your instruction
按照你的指示
I killed Kang Geon.
我杀了姜建。
Heesung and Jungbae...
熙成和正裴...
...they are clean.
……他们很干净。
Well done. Take a break.
做得好。休息一下。
Who was that, boss?
老板那人是谁？
Nobody.
没有人。
Prost.
普罗斯特。
If you think about it...
如果你想一想...
Yes, Boss?
是吗，老板？
You and me. We were always together, right?
你和我。 我们一直在一起，对吧？
Don't we both know that for sure, boss?
老板，我们俩不是都清楚这一点吗？
Son of pre-school stationer, Choi Jungbae.
学前文具店员崔正培的儿子。
Why are you talking about the old days? It is strange.
为什么要说起旧时光呢？ 它很奇怪。
Are you drunk?
你醉了吗？
As the only student
作为唯一的学生
Yeoksam High
驿三高中
Did you have an apartment?
你有公寓吗？
I was the only one living in half a basement.
我是唯一一个住 在半个地下室的人。
The poor.
穷人。
Since it's just the two of us here,
因为这里只有我们两个人，
do not meet with the Chinese yourself,
自己不去见 中国人，
because there is something important?
因为有重要的事情？
There is nothing.
没有什么。
Boss, like you said,
老板，就像你说的，
I have accompanied you all my life.
我 陪伴了你一生。
I can read your mind pretty well.
我可以很好地读懂你的想法。
Is it because of that woman, Yu Euijeong?
是因为那个女人， 柳义正吗？
-Jungbae. -Ja, Boss?
-正裴。 -贾，老板？
If you can read my mind,
如果你能读懂我的心思
you should be able to look away too .
你也应该能够把目光移开 。
You're right. But it doesn't make any sense.
你说得对。 但这没有任何意义。
You can't marry a police officer.
你不能嫁给警察。
I can not?
我不能？
Please?
请？
They marry?
他们结婚了？
Oh.
哦。
Honestly, I'm a little scared.
老实说， 我有点害怕。
What if something bad happens because of her?
万一 因为她出了什么不好的事情怎么办？
I just want you to be clear
我只是想让你清楚
that you are starting something very dangerous.
你 正在开始一些非常危险的事情。
Some things are dangerous
有些事情是危险的
but worth a try, right?
但值得一试，对吧？
And.
和。
True.
真的。
Let's drink to that.
让我们为此干杯吧。
Hey.
嘿。
How are you?
你好吗？
Choi Jungbae.
崔正培.
And, Sir?
那么，先生？
Do you trust me?
你信任我吗？
I trust them.
我相信他们。
I trust you too.
我也相信你。
Jung Gicheul is starting to trust me.
郑基哲开始信任我了。
From now on, whenever I'm free...
从现在开始，只要有空...
Stop. Let's not talk about it now.
停止。我们 现在不谈这个了。
I don't want to think about it.
我不想去想它。
Ok.
好的。
I just want to think about us.
我只是想想想我们。
Correct.
正确的。
Your mother.
你的母亲。
Was the funeral okay?
葬礼还好吗？
I'm sorry.
对不起。
And your injury?
那你的伤呢？
Are you all right?
你没事儿吧？
Yes I'm fine.
是的，我没事。
Eat up.
吃饱吧
You asshole.
你这个混蛋。
You're distracting me, you asshole.
你在分散我的注意力，你这个混蛋。
Think about it.
想一想。
Don’t you think Gicheul trusts Seungho too much?
你不觉得 Gicheul太信任Seungho了吗？
What's wrong now?
现在怎么了？
Does it bother me that he sent it?
他寄来的这件事让我烦恼吗？
to the important meeting, and not us.
参加重要会议， 而不是我们。
But you have a little free time.
但你有一点空闲时间。
When he said "important appointment"
当他说“重要的约会”时
Did he mean a date with the policewoman, you know?
他的意思是和女警察约会，你知道吗？
However, that bothers me too.
然而，这也困扰着我。
Or?
或者？
Doesn't matter. It's his business.
没关系。这是他的事。
Let's take care of ours.
让我们照顾好我们的吧。
Yoon Wongil. Did time for meth and went to China.
尹元一. 花了时间吸毒 ，然后去了中国。
Check if she is this Chinese guest.
查一下她 是不是这位中国客人。
INCHEON PASSAGIER-TERMINAL
仁川客运码头
Dear passengers...
亲爱的乘客...
Are you from Mr. Jung?
您是郑先生的吗？
Yes that's me.
是的，这就是我。
Let's go.
我们走吧。
I said somewhere nice.
我说有个 好地方。
I wanted to visit the church. It is a long time ago.
我想去参观教堂。 那是很久以前的事了。
Is that ok?
这可以吗？
Naturally.
自然。
It would be nice,
那就太好了，
when your mother went to church again.
当你母亲 再次去教堂时。
As far as I know,
据我所知，
if you are from China,
如果你来自中国，
Only Korean Chinese over 55 can enter Korea.
只有55岁以上的朝鲜族华人 才能进入韩国。
That's why I did n't expect anyone so young.
所以我没 想到会有这么年轻的人。
We don't do something like this unprepared.
我们不会在毫无准备的情况下做这样的事情。
I wasn't expecting a Korean woman.
我没想到会是一个韩国女人。
I am Korean-Chinese.
我是韩裔中国人。
And I didn't expect someone so naive.
而且我没 想到有人这么天真。
Does the person you came with take a taxi?
和你一起来的人 坐出租车吗？
Because of the recent breakdown...
因为最近的故障...
I would like to apologize.
我想道歉。
We are very sorry.
我们很抱歉。
Is this typical Korea?
这是典型的韩国吗？
let others apologize for you?
让别人 替你道歉？
One makes a mistake,
一个人犯了一个错误，
the other apologizes.
另一个道歉。
Very interesting.
很有意思。
Get some rest.
休息一下。
Your name?
你的名字？
I'm Kwon Seungho.
我是权胜浩。
They are Korean Chinese.
他们是朝鲜族中国人。
Their passports must be fake, investigations are pointless.
他们的护照肯定是假的， 调查毫无意义。
I wonder why they came to Korea.
我想知道他们为什么 来韩国。
To hand the material over to land now ?
现在把材料交给陆地吗？
Customs in Incheon would not be easy to get through.
仁川的海关 不太容易通过。
It has to be something else.
它必须是别的东西。
Let's watch them.
让我们看看他们。
What are you actually doing here?
你到底在这里做什么？
Shouldn't you be with Gicheul?
你不是应该和吉切尔在一起吗？
I'll do this here.
我会在这里做这个。
Jung Gicheul is currently
郑基哲目前
with Inspector Yu.
和于探长。
Why is Euijeong meeting him?
义正为何会遇见他？
Didn't you see what the bastard did at the funeral?
你没看到 那个混蛋在葬礼上做了什么吗？
Since you were injured, she wanted to help us.
既然你受伤了， 她想帮助我们。
Why ...
为什么 ...
Why is Euijeong helping us now?
为什么义正现在要帮助我们？
Damn, I should be faced with such a decision
妈的，我竟然要 面临这样的决定
not be asked first?
不先问吗？
It was urgent, there was no time for it.
事情很紧急， 没有时间。
We couldn't just watch.
我们不能只是看着。
-Inspector You see it well too. -Verdammt.
-督察 你也看得很清楚。 -Verdammt。
She insisted on doing everything she could to help you.
她坚持 尽一切努力来帮助你。
You trust her, don't you?
你信任她，不是吗？
Don't think too much about it.
别想太多。
Thanks to her, these are potential Chinese drug producers
多亏了她，这些都是潜在的 中国药品生产商
right before our eyes.
就在我们眼前。
Damned.
该死的。
Excuse me.
打扰一下。
Subtitles by: Ingo Krallmann
字幕：Ingo Krallmann